<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on Krishna Patel</title>
    <link>http://krishnapatel02.github.io/projects/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on Krishna Patel</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://krishnapatel02.github.io/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Simple Weather App</title>
      <link>http://krishnapatel02.github.io/projects/weather_app/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://krishnapatel02.github.io/projects/weather_app/</guid>
      <description>Introduction: A weather app made for Android using Kotlin. To get the weather data the app uses Android&amp;rsquo;s volley library to make an API request using the user&amp;rsquo;s location and then the response is parsed using a JSON library. The data is all obtained from the OpenWeatherAPI. There is also a toggle for Farenheit and Celcius and a search box to look up the weather in a different location.
Github Link: Link will be added once project is at a finished state.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unraid Server</title>
      <link>http://krishnapatel02.github.io/projects/unraid_server/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://krishnapatel02.github.io/projects/unraid_server/</guid>
      <description>Introduction: This server will be used for multiple applications through virtualization. Unraid is a linux distro that allows the partitioning of resources to virtual machines/ The VMs will be used to run multiple servers/docker containers: one for a game server, one for media serving over the local network, and the last for miscellaneous development use.
Hardware: CPU: Intel Core i7 4960X 6 Core Processor RAM: 32GB DDR3 8GB x 4 SSD: 256GB Hard Drives: 1TB 3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Various Data Structures in Python</title>
      <link>http://krishnapatel02.github.io/projects/data_structures_313/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://krishnapatel02.github.io/projects/data_structures_313/</guid>
      <description>Introduction: Linked below is a link to a python file with an implementation of a queue, stack, priority queue, binary search tree, and red-black tree. This code was written for a data structures course.
Github Link: Placeholder</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
